Yeehaw
Baby I’ve been to a couple rodeos
But the place that I’m headed ain’t got no roads
So tell me if you down for a helluva ride
And hop up on this saddle and hold real tight
So giddy up (hyah, hyah)
Even if it’s just for the night
My life, real fast
Check my wallet, no cash
Few beers in my tummy
Make me wanna ride through the wide open country
No one's around me
Wind in my face, heart beating as I race
Who can change my goddamn mind
Baby I’ve been to a couple rodeos
But the place that I’m headed ain’t got no roads
So tell me if you down for a helluva ride
And hop up on this saddle and hold real tight
So giddy up (hyah, hyah)
Even if it’s just for the night
I came, I saw
With the reigns straight gripped up in my paws
She felt, on me
New boots yeah you know they Balmain
No one's around me
Wind in my face, heart beating as I race
Who can change my goddamn mind
(gahdamn)
Baby I’ve been to a couple rodeos
But the place that I’m headed ain’t got no roads
So tell me if you down for a helluva ride
And hop up on this saddle and hold real tight
So giddy up